Guide to the Fredericka Martin Photograph Collection ALBA.PHOTO.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Photographs, circa 1937-1938
  - Medical Personnel: Mike Hill and Oscar Weissman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Medical Personnel: Mike Hill, Pat ?, Beryl ?, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Medical Personnel: Operating, Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Medical Personnel: Operating, Edward Barsky and Oscar Israel Weissman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Medical Personnel: Oscar Weissman, Anne Taft, ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Medical Personnel: Preparing Plaster Bandages, Teruel Front and Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Medical Personnel: Rebecca Wachsman and Augusto ? with Burros, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Medical Personnel: Rose Sara Goldblatt, Phyllis Hilbert, Anne Taft, Spanish Aid, Angelita ?, Seguro de los Ba?É¬±os, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Medical Personnel: Rose Sara Goldblatt, Toby Jensky, ? Townsen, ? Sivens, ? Quinones, Santiago Leal, Lucia Lirio, Aragon, Dec 14, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Medical Personnel: Rose Sara Goldblatt, ?, Dorothy Fontaine, ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Medical Personnel: Salle 9, Matar?É¬?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Medical Personnel: Shipboard, Back Row (L to R) Dr. Castro, Caesare ?, Tate ?, ?; Middle Row (L to R), Edna Drabkin Romer, Fredericka Martin, ? Faller, May Edythe Dyer, Mary Rader, Selma Chadwick; Front Row (L to R), Dr., circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Medical Personnel: Showering Women, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Angelita ?, Ferriouda Herrero, Pepita ?, Jerry ?, ?, Uiva ?, ?, ? Voloklein, ?, ?, ?, ?, Taran?É¬ßon, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Barcelona, Apr 21, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Saying Goodbye to John Jacob Posner and Staff, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, ?, Andrea Muniz, Petra Diaz, ?, ?, Constancia ?, Emelia ?, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, ?, Rosita ?, Madrid, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Medical Personnel: Spanish, At the Beach, Port Bou, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Medical Personnel: Stretcher-Bearers, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Medical Personnel: Surgery, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Medical Personnel: Valcarca Hospital, Barcelona, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Medical Tent: With Unidentified Woman, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Medical Vehicles: Ambulances from U.S., Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Memorials to International Brigade: Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Menhoff, Dr.: Group, ?, ?, ?, ?, ? (Women), Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Merims, Sonia: Group, ?, ?, ?, ?, ?, (Men), Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Merims, Sonia: George Moser and Spanish Children, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Mexican Volunteer: Portrait, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Militiamen: Marching, Valencia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Miller, Benjamin: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Miller, William: Contact Sheet with Portrait of Miller, Edward Lending, Lester Gittleson, Johnny Bernard, Congressman Jerry O'Connel, undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Miller, William: Contact Sheet of Images from Miller's Photo Album, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Minor, Robert: Donald H. Pitts, Villa Paz, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Moser, George C.: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Murcia Hospital: Recovery Room, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Murcia Hospital: Treating a Patient, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Nance, Youngblood: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Oliva Campillo, Juan: Family, Spain, May 29, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Palestinian Nurse "Ruth": Poolside, University Hospital, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Palestinian Nurse "Ruth": Poolside with Spanish Youth, University Hospital, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Pasionara Hospital: Buildings, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pasionara Hospital: Ruth Epstein, Dora Donda, Hermine Hartman, Lisa Nommiot, Lisa Gavric, Edith ?, Hilda Bell, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Paul Valliant Couturier: Children's Camp, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pelegrini, Antonio: In Operating Room, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Pelegrini, Antonio: Group, Manuel ?, Jose ?, Sitting on Ambulance, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Perez, Odio: Al Steine, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Perez, Odio: Group, Toby Jensky at Fiesta, Castillejo, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Pike, Florence (a.k.a. Florence Mildred Tew): En Route to Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pike, Florence (a.k.a. Florence Mildred Tew): En Route to Spain, Rose Wachsman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Pike, William: In Operating Room, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Pike, William: In Tree, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Pike, William: Shaking a Woman's Hand, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Pike, William: with Unidentified Woman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Pike, William: with Wife, Post-SCW, U.S. [?], undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Pilar, Liam: Group, Unidentified Children and Men, Japan, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Pilar, Liam: Portrait, NYC, May 9, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Pilar, Liam: Unidentified Woman, Spain [?], circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Pitts, Donald H.: At the Front, Non-Combat, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Pitts, Donald H.: with Two Others, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pitts, Donald H.: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Pitts, Williams: At the Front, Non-Combat, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pool, Nick: Groups, Unidentified, Vich, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Jaw Surgery Patients, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Lenora Temple, Mathilda Jankovic, Dulcea Hernaiz, Rebecca Shulman, Evelyn Rahman, Rose Weiner, Epiphanio Lopez, Jose Simon Gonzalez, Martha Mitchell, with Two Others, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, M. Zachary Stadt, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Martha Mitchell and Patients, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Group, Martha Mitchell, M. Zachary Stadt and Unidentified Group, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Posner, John Jacob: Spanish Patient and Black Sheep, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Pozo Blanco: Unidentified Volunteers, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Pretecalle, Ojier: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Purviance, Katherine: Group, Children, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Rackley, Mildred: Carol Rahman and Ambulance, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Rackley, Mildred: Family, Not in Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Rader, Mary: Shipboard, Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Demonstrations, NYC, 1935-1936 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Dombrowski Brigade, Barcelona, Jul 10, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Paintings, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Rauschwald, Mark: Residence in NYC, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Raven, Robert J.: Kissing Fernanda Good-Bye, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Recovering Patients: General/Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Recovering Patients: Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Reissing, Herman F.: Portrait with Wife, Not in Spain, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Roemer, Edna: Group, Jack Devine, Charles DeSevelskoe, Norman Rontz, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Roffman, Joe: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Romer, Sam: Portrait, Not in Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - El Romeral: Nursing School, Tarancon, [1970s] (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - El Romeral Hospital: Buildings, Tarancon, Summer 1937 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - El Romeral Hospital: (Center) Helen Freeman, Mildred Rackley (Left) Anne Taft (Right) Pierre Queignac (Front) Rose Freed, Ray Harris, Fredericka Martin, Tarancon, Feb 16, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - El Romeral Hospital: Laboratory/Pharmacy, Tarancon, Feb 1, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - El Romeral Hospital: Male Nurses Aides Making Plaster Bandages, Tarancon, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Rubin, Henry: Groups, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Rubin, Henry: Mobile Blood Transfusion Unit, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Rubin, Henry: Operating Room, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Rubin, Henry: Portraits, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Ruiz, Jose: Ambulance Driver, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Saelices Hospital: Children's Festival, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Salon: Almira, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Sanchez, Ramon: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Saulhen, Frank: At the Front, Non-Combat, Cordoba Front, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Schuetrum, Walter J.: At the Front, Non-Combat, Juan ?, Pete Smith, "Southgate", Mac Kraus, ?, Hal Smith, ? Govett, Spain, Apr 21, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Schuldiner, Anne: Shipboard, Two Nurses and ?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Schulman, Rebecca: Family and Friends, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Schuman, Rebecca: Group, Irving Busch, Ramen Durem and Four Others, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Schulman, Rebecca: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Schuman, Rebecca: Unidentified Man, Not in Spain, [1935] (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Schuman, Rebecca: Unidentified Man and Woman, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Schulman, Rebecca: Unidentified Nurses, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Seminar Hospital: Taran?É¬ßon, Dec 1, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Service Internationale pour l'Enfance: Group, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Shipboard: Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Shuldiner, Anne: Shipboard with Two Nurses and One Man, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Silverstein, Esther: Portrait, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Siqueiros, David Alfaro: Mural, [Mexico], undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Smith, Bill: Portrait with Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Smith, John: Portrait, NYC, undated (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Smithson, Beryl: Michael [Erceg ?], Belcazar Hospital, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Soler y Tarafa, Oscar: En Route to Spain, Family Farewell, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Sonnenberg, Randall: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Spanish Army Hospitals: Baeza, Ubeda, Jaen Province, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Barcelona, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Castillejo, Seg?É¬?briaga, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Figueras, Jun 1, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Godella, Aug 1, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Madrid, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Photographic Postcards, Madrid, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Taran?É¬ßon, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Valencia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Spanish Cities: Street Scenes, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Spanish Civilians, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Spanish Civilians: Almeria, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Spanish Civilians: Children, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Spanish Civilians: Children, Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Spanish Civilians: Shepherd, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Spanish Civilians: Workers, Laundrywomen, circa 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Spanish Civilians: Workers, Laundrywomen and M. Zachary Stadt, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Spanish Landscapes, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Puy Del Mas, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Sabinosa, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Spanish Landscapes: Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Spanish Nurse: Portrait, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Spanish Nurses: Groups, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Spanish Villages: Street Scenes, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Sparrow, ?: with Six Men, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Sparrow, ?: with Unidentified Woman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Stadt, M. Zachary: Group, Hilda Bell (Roberts), ? Gomez, ? Prieto, ? Balans, Shipboard on S.S. Normandie, May 1, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Stander, Lionel: Collecting Funds for Medical Supplies, U.S., circa 1937- 1938 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Stirchbaum, Max: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Straus, Mark: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Straus, Mark: Unidentified Doctor, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Straus, Mark: with Patient, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Student Nurses: Group, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Sueco Noruego Hospital: Buildings, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Sueco Noruego Hospital: Medical Personnel, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Swienczewski, Walter: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Taft, Anne: At the Front, Non-Combat, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Taft, Anne: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Taft, Anne: May Edith Dyer, May Levine, Grace Margolis, Matar?É¬?, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Taft, Anne: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Taft, Anne: Portrait, Not in Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Taft, Anne: Portrait, U.S., circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Taft, Anne: Surgery, A. I. Friedman and Albert Byrne, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Telfuentes, Dr.: Presenting at Panel, U.S., circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Temple, Lenora: Portrait, [Spain?], circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Temple, Lenora: Shipboard, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Tenin, Juliette: Medical Personnel, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Tenin, Juliette: Portraits, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Thompson, Louise: Portraits, U.S., undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Toch, Joseph: Portraits, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Torman, Alexander: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Towsen, Gus: Shipboard with Two Men, NYC, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Train Station: Cerbere (France), May 28, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Unidentified Group: Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - University Hospital: Lisa Gavric, Anka Bohimicki, Olga "Milica" ?Ö¬?ivkovic, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Urmston, Lillian: Operation, Teruel Front, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Van Reemst, Theodore: Portrait, Not in Spain, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Van Reemst de Vries, Trudi: Portrait, Post SCW, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Van Reemst de Vries, Trudi: Receiving Award/Flowers, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Vanzant, Frances: with Sylvia Sidney, U.S., circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Vanzant, Frances: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Vanzant, Frances: Portraits, NYC and Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Vega-Diaz, Francisco: Hospital de Andujar, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Veterans: Post-SCW, Edward O'Flaherty, William Pike, Tom ?, Daniel Samuel Groden, Oscar Hunter, Charles O'Flaherty, Not in Spain, undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Village Fair: Child with Banner, "Milk for the Children of Spain!", NYC, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Villa John Reed: Benicasim, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Villa Paz: Ambulance, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Villa Paz: Cleaning/Kitchen Staff, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Villa Paz: Flag Donated by the French, circa 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Villa Paz, Groups, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Villa Paz: Individuals, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Villa Paz: Operating Room, Apr 1, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Villa Paz: Post-SCW, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Villa Paz: Recovering Patients, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Vogel, Sidney: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Vogel, Sidney: Group, with Five Men, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Unknown Man: In Small Boat, Cerbere (France), May 1, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Vogel, Sidney: Portraits, Spain, undated, Nov 1937 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Wachsman, Rose: Family, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Wachsman, Rose: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Wachsman, Rose: Rest and Relaxation, Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Wachsman, Shipboard, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Wagnon, Alice Elizabeth: Group, Leonard H. Larson and Evelyn Andell, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Wagnon, Alice Elizabeth: Group, Unidentified, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Warton, Patrice: Group, in Vineyard, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Weber, Franz: Gurs Concentration Camp, France, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Weinstein, (?): Reading, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Weissman, Helene: Behind the Lines, Daily Life of the Soldiers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Weissman, Helene: Behind the Lines, Rest and Relaxation, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Weissman, Helene: Shipboard with Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Weissman, Helene: With Oscar Israel Weissman, Villa Paz, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Weissman, Oscar Israel: with Two Men, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Wesson, Helene: Daily Life of the Soldiers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Wilson, Una: With Unidentified Man, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Zandt, N.: Group, Three Volunteers and One Boy, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Zwnais, Jack: Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 100)
- Series II: Negatives, 1937-1973
  - Alcoy Hospital: Buildings, May 26, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Allemand, Klaus: Artwork, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - AMB: Ambulance/Autochir, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AMB: Ambulance Donated by the Negro People of America to the People of Republican Spain, Salaria Kee (a.k.a. Salaria Kea) (second from right), circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - AMB: Chauffeurs/Drivers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - AMB: Demonstrations/Fund Raising, Not in Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - AMB: Dentists, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - AMB: Doctors and Nurses, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - AMB: En Route to Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - AMB: En Route to Spain, Ambulance Unit No. VII, Thelma Erickson Edythe May Dyer, Dr. Franklin, Selma Chadwick, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - AMB: En Route to Spain, Hilda Bell, A.N. Townsen, Joseph Richard Chodoff, Rose Margaret Harvan, S.S. Normandie, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - AMB: Frank Thomas Woodbury, Leo Eloesser, Edward Barsky and Unidentified Group, circa 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - AMB: Groups, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - AMB: Individuals, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - AMB: Two Women in Spain, Evelyn Hutchins Rahman and Ruth Davidow, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - At the Front: Non-Combat, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - At the Front: Non-Combat, Toby Jensky, Odio Perez and Unidentified Group, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Barsky, Edward, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Behind the Lines: Daily Life of the Soldiers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Behind the Lines: Daily Life of the Soldiers, Dutch Volunteers, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, ?, Judson Briggs, ?, Dave Davidson, Barcelona, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 22a)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, Albert Byrne and Thelma Erickson, Apr 20, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Behind the Lines: Rest and Relaxation, Karl Rahman, Evelyn Hutchins with Three Others, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Bell, Hilda: Images from Photo Album, Murcia, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Benicasim Hospital, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Bombed/Shelled Buildings, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Briggs, Judson: Groups and Portrait, Spain, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Epstein, Ruth, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - El Escorial Hospital: Buildings, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Fuhr (DeVries), Lini: (center) and Unidentified Group, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Goland, Philip Pakier, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Groups: Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Hecht, Anne, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Homenaje, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Hospital: Recovery Ward, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Individuals: Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Injured/Recovering Patients, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Medical Personnel: Dutch, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Medical Personnel: En Route to Spain, ? Murhy, ? Faubion, Morris Miller, ? Lockett, ? Goldrick, ? Vazquez, ? Hansen, ? Bleir, ? Ransom, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Medical Personnel: Groups, Unidentified, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Medical Personnel: Surgery, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Medical Personnel: Surgery, Albert Byrne, Anne Taft and Oscar Weissman, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Militiawomen, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Miller, William Colfax: Certificado de Baja, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Posters/Artwork, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Refugees, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Spanish Civilians, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Spanish Civilians: Children, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Spanish Civilians: Women, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Van Reemst de Vries, Trudi: Portrait, circa 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Silde: Latin American Woman and Child, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Series III: Photo Albums, circa 1937-1938
  - Red Photo Album, circa 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_2c5d4c2eb67c9e32a1a1c1d9b71c0fc1)